<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-04-12T04:43:37+00:00</updated><id>https://somaticbalance.com.au/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Balance by Celeste</title><subtitle>Balance by Celeste</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Online Somatic Explorations &amp;amp; Meditations</title><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/community/somatic%20explorations/2020/03/24/online-somatic-meditation-course/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Online Somatic Explorations &amp; Meditations" /><published>2020-03-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://somaticbalance.com.au/community/somatic%20explorations/2020/03/24/online-somatic-meditation-course</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://somaticbalance.com.au/community/somatic%20explorations/2020/03/24/online-somatic-meditation-course/">&lt;p&gt;In these uncertain times, it’s equally important and challenging to be present and stay grounded. And that’s why I’m
offering these &lt;strong&gt;Somatic Meditations and Explorations&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal of this series is to support and deepen the process of coming back to the body, increasing somatic awareness
and connection to the present moment, through a succession of movement explorations and embodiment practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are welcome to practice with us no matter where you are at on your journey. The regular practice of these
embodiments and meditations can support you and bring many benefits, such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• increasing your body awareness, and contact with the present.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• releasing tension and improving posture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• enhancing breathing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• achieving a greater sense of balance and stability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• and since body and mind cannot be separate, you might notice more openness toward the environment and other
people, a sense of security and more energy overall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following series have been inspired by my training in Rolfing, Embodied Counselling, Yoga -and some other
modalities- as well as on my own explorations of different types of somatic movement
practices, such as Hanna Somatics, Feldenkrais, and Rolfing movement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are meeting &lt;strong&gt;every Monday at 8:15 AM Sydney Time&lt;/strong&gt; to explore together for 15 minutes. These sessions are free of
charge and all you have to do is &lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot;&gt;contact me&lt;/a&gt; expressing your interest, and I’ll send you all the info so you
can join us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those wanting deeper explorations, I’m offering 10 weeks of guided practice in reduced online groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;course-details&quot;&gt;Course details&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Duration: 10 sessions/ 1x week - 45 minutes per session&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Reduced groups (7 people max.) - Via Zoom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cost for the for the entire series is $180 (upfront payment - and if you miss a class I’ll send the video of the corresponding session so you don’t miss it).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the moment there are 2 groups/times available to start in April:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;◦ Mondays 9:00 am (AEST)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;◦  Thursdays 9:00 am (AEST)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d love to see you there! Get in touch today and let’s explore together!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">In these uncertain times, it’s equally important and challenging to be present and stay grounded. And that’s why I’m offering these Somatic Meditations and Explorations.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://source.unsplash.com/Yui5vfKHuzs/2000x1322?a=.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://source.unsplash.com/Yui5vfKHuzs/2000x1322?a=.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Presenting: The Bookworms Cavern</title><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/community/2020/02/20/the-bookworms-cavern/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Presenting: The Bookworms Cavern" /><published>2020-02-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-02-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://somaticbalance.com.au/community/2020/02/20/the-bookworms-cavern</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://somaticbalance.com.au/community/2020/02/20/the-bookworms-cavern/">&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wished you could “read” someone? Maybe take a peek through their past stories and hopes for the future,
understand which pages of their life they have bookmarked as great memories? Well, now we might just be able to do that.
Introducing my latest project…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My inspiration comes from books - all those beautiful books out there waiting for us to reach out and make them our
companions and friends - and people - all those beautiful people out there waiting for …well, pretty much the same as
books, right? So how about creating a book club that’s about people instead of books? I can almost hear you say “What is
she talking about?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I present to you &lt;em&gt;“The Bookworm’s Cavern”&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• We get together every 3 weeks. No tickets, or cost or anything like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• You’re invited to bring one book with you that stood out in some way: it was the best you’ve ever read, the one that
inspired you to make some kind of change in your life, maybe it was the worst book you’ve ever read, or the most boring
one, maybe it’s the one you bought 3 years ago because you liked the cover and never got to read it, maybe it’s a
dictionary, maybe it’s the only one you have… doesn’t really matter, just one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Through your experience with that book others are invited to have a peek into who you really are. By sharing what the
book meant to you, how you changed with it, how you felt, or why you hate the cover, you are sharing a piece of yourself
through it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• We have a drink together; feel, talk, laugh or cry as needed, and then say goodbye with a hug (maybe?), and repeat
all of that again in 3 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-am-i-expecting-will-happen&quot;&gt;What am I expecting will happen?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, for starters have some fun, meet people and be surrounded by books… that
alone sounds good enough to me. Maybe we’ll make friends, or read more and discover new books. Well, we’ll see about that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-im-not-expecting-will-happen&quot;&gt;What I’m not expecting will happen?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We all have to read the same book, or talk about it, or reflect on something, or
follow a tight structure, or workshop our life…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;when-are-we-meeting&quot;&gt;When are we meeting?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every three weeks on Thursday from 6:30 to 8:30 pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested? If so please &lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot;&gt;get it touch&lt;/a&gt; so I can add you to “The Bookworm’s Cavern” mailing list and keep you
posted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there and maybe borrow a book from you some time ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;COVID-19 is not stopping us! We’re just meeting in a virtual space for now.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Have you ever wished you could “read” someone? Maybe take a peek through their past stories and hopes for the future, understand which pages of their life they have bookmarked as great memories? Well, now we might just be able to do that. Introducing my latest project…</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://source.unsplash.com/6pO3QFkk7hQ/2000x1322?a=.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://source.unsplash.com/6pO3QFkk7hQ/2000x1322?a=.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">My love affair with Rolfing</title><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/rolfing/2020/01/27/my-love-affair-with-rolfing/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My love affair with Rolfing" /><published>2020-01-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://somaticbalance.com.au/rolfing/2020/01/27/my-love-affair-with-rolfing</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://somaticbalance.com.au/rolfing/2020/01/27/my-love-affair-with-rolfing/">&lt;p&gt;Books are magic and marvelous things, wouldn’t you agree? They’ve taught me much, they’ve made me laugh and cry, and
they’ve laid in front of me many hidden treasures for which I’m forever grateful. And Rolfing was one of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I first read about it I swear it was love at first sight. It just made so much sense, you know? My mind had such a
crush with it and the concept of using gravity as an ally to help your body thrive. After all, we are born into gravity,
and it’s probably as important to us as the air that we breathe, or the sun that gives life. Gravity is always there,
and this brilliant woman called Ida P. Rolf, not only saw that but she developed an approach to bodywork that uses
gravity to free our bodies, to help us be comfortable again, to help us stop struggling. And to me, that’s worth a
crush.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I immediately wanted to understand, study and read more - I usually do, you see, but this time it was not only about
letting my mind go on with its new crush. No. This time it was my body the only one who could say if what was written in
those books was true. So I booked in for a session, asked my mind to be quiet for a while, and let my body decide. Is
this crush worth it? Could this be true love?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And let me tell you, in that first session I fell head over heels for it. What a pleasure to be touched in such a
different way - there was no agenda, no trying to fix my body because something was wrong with it, not trying to tell me
what I should do, not forcing anything. It felt like a physical reminder of the possibilities of comfort, movement and
freedom that had always been available for my body, but I somehow had forgotten. It felt like being brought back to
myself - as if with each session we were reminding my body of its natural and organic order and alignment. I felt
included in the sessions - this wasn’t something being done on me. No. This was something we were doing together;
something we were discovering together. And I loved every minute of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So in the 10-sessions process my body-mind fell deeply in love with Rolfing, and I went on to study it to understand
more. And I’ve received many, many sessions - from teachers, classmates, colleagues- and I’ve loved all of them.
Sometimes there was confusion as my body-mind was trying to adapt to the new possibilities. Sometimes there was pain as
I was letting go of old tensions that had been with me way too long. Sometimes there was silence, as something new
seemed to emerge. Always there was a coming back to myself, to feeling freer, more present, more comfortable in my own
skin, more alive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So when somebody asks me why I became a Rolfer, I always find it hard to explain. Do I talk to them about having a
crush? About falling in love? About the tension that disappeared? About how my breath changed? About how my body-mind
found comfort from the inside? I’m still not sure. I’d really rather invite them to try, so they can feel it and maybe
then they’ll understand why I fell in love, and why this love affair is still going on.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Books are magic and marvelous things, wouldn’t you agree? They’ve taught me much, they’ve made me laugh and cry, and they’ve laid in front of me many hidden treasures for which I’m forever grateful. And Rolfing was one of them.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://somaticbalance.com.au/images/love-letter.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://somaticbalance.com.au/images/love-letter.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">How I beat the shoulds</title><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/somatic%20explorations/2019/11/27/how-i-beat-the-shoulds/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How I beat the shoulds" /><published>2019-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://somaticbalance.com.au/somatic%20explorations/2019/11/27/how-i-beat-the-shoulds</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://somaticbalance.com.au/somatic%20explorations/2019/11/27/how-i-beat-the-shoulds/">&lt;p&gt;Let me tell you a story that started many years ago, in a far away land… It’s 2011 and she’s just moved to one of the
most exciting cities in the world. If you looked at her, you would know how happy she is. See? She’s in her early
thirties and in a great romantic relationship (mmm people in love!). Her job is well-paid and covers all the bills and
some more, her yoga practice is solid, her diet is great, and there’s even a tiny cute garden in her apartment’s balcony
where she can sit and read. What else could she ask for? She’s so happy, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well… she’s not. Everyone thinks she inhabits a world of happiness but she’s a prisoner of her Shoulds. Oh my, so many
Shoulds… She tries really hard to be who she Should be around her friends. Accepted the job everyone though she Should
accept. And feels only those feelings she’s supposed to fell. You Should see her: she never gets angry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And she knows it. She didn’t at first, because achieving all those Shoulds kind of felt great. But not anymore. Now she
knows. It’s not like she can put words around it and explain it to others. But trust me, she’s not happy. She can feel
something is off… terribly off. But what is it? How can she know? Everything is as it Should. What could be wrong?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is. She’s the one that’s off. She’s the one that got lost in all those Shoulds and got replaced by a
this-is-how-you-are-supposed-to-be version of herself. She can’t see it clearly yet but she can feel it. And it’s eating
her inside. And she tries to talk to others as best as she can, but it doesn’t work because, you see, they all think the
Shoulds are fine, and she Should just be happy and get over it. She keeps searching, not because she knows what she’s
looking for but because there’s really no other choice for her. She’s not ready to give up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then, by a stroke of luck, she finds a spark, and a faint light seems to go on inside her and she dives into it.
She doesn’t know it yet but this is her first contact with a somatic practice. The first time she’s invited to feel her
body, and let me tell you, I can hear her thinking “Sorry, what?? Feel my body? What do you mean? What Should I do?” And
her teacher - who’s now her mentor and good friend - sees her, smiles at her, and with infinite patience starts to
support and guide her back to herself, through her emotions; back into herself through being present; back into herself
through her body… and it takes time, and it takes work, and it takes showing up when it’s hard, and it takes effort, and
then, the day you least expect it, the light inside her goes on, and it’s bright, and she’s back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, actually, I’m back. Because now I’m present in me, I’m embodied, and I can live here and now. And all those
shoulds, well there’s no space for them in my body now, so they don’t bother me as much, and when they do come back, I
go back to my body, to my breath, and I see they are there but not part of me anymore. And then I can breathe. And then
I can live and be me. Not the best version of me. Not the right version of me. Not the desired version of me. Just me.
As I am now. As I choose to be. As I accept myself to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then my mind goes back to her in 2011. Did she know? Did she make that effort just to save me? Did she commit to it
so I could be happy today? I know she did. And I thank her every step of the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So now that’s why I do what I do. So others can also beat their Shoulds, make space to breathe and be. And maybe also
look back and thanks themselves.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Let me tell you a story that started many years ago, in a far away land… It’s 2011 and she’s just moved to one of the most exciting cities in the world. If you looked at her, you would know how happy she is. See? She’s in her early thirties and in a great romantic relationship (mmm people in love!). Her job is well-paid and covers all the bills and some more, her yoga practice is solid, her diet is great, and there’s even a tiny cute garden in her apartment’s balcony where she can sit and read. What else could she ask for? She’s so happy, right?</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://somaticbalance.com.au/images/graffiti.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://somaticbalance.com.au/images/graffiti.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>