<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-04-25T04:17:22+00:00</updated><id>https://somaticbalance.com.au/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Balance by Celeste</title><subtitle>Balance by Celeste</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Video: Opening your body through the breath</title><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/videos/somatic%20explorations/2020/04/24/opening-the-body-through-breath/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Video: Opening your body through the breath" /><published>2020-04-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-04-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://somaticbalance.com.au/videos/somatic%20explorations/2020/04/24/opening-the-body-through-breath</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://somaticbalance.com.au/videos/somatic%20explorations/2020/04/24/opening-the-body-through-breath/">&lt;p&gt;This short practice is perfect for those moments where everything seems to be too much and we can’t find space for
ourselves. You can use it as many times as you need during the day, to simply take a break from what’s happening ‘out
there’ and reconnect to yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;padding:56.25% 0 0 0;position:relative;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/408246718?color=a6c7bd&amp;amp;byline=0&amp;amp;portrait=0&quot; style=&quot;position:absolute;top:0;left:0;width:100%;height:100%;&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; fullscreen&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/api/player.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to learn how to develop a deeper practice, chat to us about 1:1 &lt;a href=&quot;/modalities/somatic-explorations/&quot;&gt;Somatic Explorations&lt;/a&gt;
where you can explore and be supported as you gain a deeper understanding of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This short practice is perfect for those moments where everything seems to be too much and we can’t find space for ourselves. You can use it as many times as you need during the day, to simply take a break from what’s happening ‘out there’ and reconnect to yourself.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://source.unsplash.com/Jd2fqoX3z_0/2000x1322?a=.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://source.unsplash.com/Jd2fqoX3z_0/2000x1322?a=.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Mindfulness menu</title><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/somatic%20explorations/2020/04/18/mindfulness-menu/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mindfulness menu" /><published>2020-04-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-04-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://somaticbalance.com.au/somatic%20explorations/2020/04/18/mindfulness-menu</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://somaticbalance.com.au/somatic%20explorations/2020/04/18/mindfulness-menu/">&lt;p&gt;It can be difficult to tend to our needs when we don’t exactly know what to do especially during high-stress moments.
To help with that, we’ve designed a Mindfulness Menu where you can fill-in-the-blanks with bite-sized mindfulness
practices that work for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leave it on your fridge or take a picture of it, so you always have a handy guide to turn to. 
&lt;a href=&quot;/res/mindfulness_menu.pdf&quot;&gt;Download the printable template&lt;/a&gt; and check out some of our favourite ideas below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/mindfulness_menu_by_cele.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;menu&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’d love to hear about the ideas that would go on your Mindfulness Menu!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot;&gt;Contact us&lt;/a&gt; or tag us on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/balancebyceleste/&quot;&gt;Instagram @balancebyceleste&lt;/a&gt; with a
picture of your menu. If you are needing additional support at the moment or want to learn how to deepen your
mindfulness practice, we are available for online sessions.
Drop us a message for more information: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:hello@somaticbalance.com.au&quot;&gt;hello@somaticbalance.com.au&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It can be difficult to tend to our needs when we don’t exactly know what to do especially during high-stress moments. To help with that, we’ve designed a Mindfulness Menu where you can fill-in-the-blanks with bite-sized mindfulness practices that work for you.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://source.unsplash.com/7Od26RsZ2Rk/2000x1322?a=.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://source.unsplash.com/7Od26RsZ2Rk/2000x1322?a=.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Video: Softening your shoulders</title><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/videos/somatic%20explorations/2020/04/12/releasing-tension-of-the-shoulders/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Video: Softening your shoulders" /><published>2020-04-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-04-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://somaticbalance.com.au/videos/somatic%20explorations/2020/04/12/releasing-tension-of-the-shoulders</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://somaticbalance.com.au/videos/somatic%20explorations/2020/04/12/releasing-tension-of-the-shoulders/">&lt;p&gt;Carrying tension on your shoulders? Stiff neck? Join us in this practice and find a simple way to allow your shoulders
to soften. The best part? It takes less than 5 minutes, and you can practice it anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;padding:56.25% 0 0 0;position:relative;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/408244968?color=a6c7bd&amp;amp;byline=0&amp;amp;portrait=0&quot; style=&quot;position:absolute;top:0;left:0;width:100%;height:100%;&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; fullscreen&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/api/player.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to learn how to develop a deeper practice, chat to us about 1:1 &lt;a href=&quot;/modalities/somatic-explorations/&quot;&gt;Somatic Explorations&lt;/a&gt;
where you can explore and be supported as you gain a deeper understanding of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Carrying tension on your shoulders? Stiff neck? Join us in this practice and find a simple way to allow your shoulders to soften. The best part? It takes less than 5 minutes, and you can practice it anywhere.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://source.unsplash.com/3vc6pAclY-4/2000x1322?a=.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://source.unsplash.com/3vc6pAclY-4/2000x1322?a=.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">What do you really need?</title><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/somatic%20explorations/2020/04/05/asking-for-what-you-need/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What do you really need?" /><published>2020-04-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-04-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://somaticbalance.com.au/somatic%20explorations/2020/04/05/asking-for-what-you-need</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://somaticbalance.com.au/somatic%20explorations/2020/04/05/asking-for-what-you-need/">&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-quote&quot;&gt;“When we express our needs indirectly through the use of evaluations, interpretations, and images, others are likely to hear criticism. And when people hear anything that sounds like criticism, they tend to invest their energy in self-defense or counterattack. If we wish for a compassionate response from others, it is self-defeating to express our needs by interpreting or diagnosing their behavior. Instead, the more directly we can connect our feelings to our own needs, the easier it is for others to respond to us compassionately.”

- Marshall B. Rosenberg, Nonviolent Communication: A Language of Life: Life-Changing Tools for Healthy Relationships
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This time, we’re turning our minds to the ideas and insights around non-violent communication. This form of
communication teaches us that, to be able to connect with our needs, we first have to gain clarity about what’s alive in
us. In any given situation, there are many points of views and sometimes we’re quick to assume why others behave the way
they do. This can create confusion and lead to endless misunderstandings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A useful way to break that vicious cycle is to pause for a moment and ask ourselves: what’s the behaviour I can observe?
What do I actually see? And then, how does that make me feel? Am I sad, angry, happy? What’s alive in my heart then? And
what are my true needs? Do I need safety? Maybe it’s acknowledgement I’m needing, or connection. And now that I know my
need, how could I make a request that helps fulfill that need, without demanding or forcing people to do what I want?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a simple practice that will help you have a deeper understanding of what you may be experiencing, and also one
that helps us get out of our heads!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Name the situation that’s troubling you: ………………………………………………&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Eg: My partner doesn’t understand me!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s see what happens when you can get more clarity by stating the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1- What’s the observable behavior or event? Not what you think, suppose or imagine, but what you actually
see/hear/observe:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I see&lt;/strong&gt; ………………………………………………&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Eg: I see them giving me advice on how to solve a problem at work.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2- What’s the fantasy that’s going on in your head about that  situation? WHat do you think/believe is happening?:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I imagine/think&lt;/strong&gt; ………………………………………………&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Eg: I imagine they want to find a solution so they won’t have to hear me talk about it.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3- What emotions are alive in you right now? Are you sad, happy, afraid, content, excited? This is not how others make
you feel (I feel abandoned), but the actual emotions you are experiencing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I feel&lt;/strong&gt; ………………………………………………&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Eg: I feel sad, lonely and afraid.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4- What’s the core need that needs to be met? Is it safety, connection, acknowledgement, love, privacy? This is not what
you want others to do, but your actual core need:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I need&lt;/strong&gt; ………………………………………………&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Eg: I need empathy and understanding. (Now we can say to our partners: “Could you please hear me out and empathise? I
don’t really need a solution right now, I just need reassurance that you are here for me.”)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you can identify your core needs, you can begin to think of ways to meet them - whether on your own or by clearly
communicating it to people you trust to support you. Try this exercise and let us know what you discover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to develop a deeper connection to your needs, chat to us about 1:1 &lt;a href=&quot;/modalities/somatic-explorations/&quot;&gt;Somatic Explorations&lt;/a&gt;
where you can explore and be supported as you gain a deeper understanding of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">```quote “When we express our needs indirectly through the use of evaluations, interpretations, and images, others are likely to hear criticism. And when people hear anything that sounds like criticism, they tend to invest their energy in self-defense or counterattack. If we wish for a compassionate response from others, it is self-defeating to express our needs by interpreting or diagnosing their behavior. Instead, the more directly we can connect our feelings to our own needs, the easier it is for others to respond to us compassionately.”</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://source.unsplash.com/oMpAz-DN-9I/2000x1322?a=.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://source.unsplash.com/oMpAz-DN-9I/2000x1322?a=.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Video: Exploring breath and space</title><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/videos/somatic%20explorations/2020/04/01/exploring-breath-and-space/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Video: Exploring breath and space" /><published>2020-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://somaticbalance.com.au/videos/somatic%20explorations/2020/04/01/exploring-breath-and-space</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://somaticbalance.com.au/videos/somatic%20explorations/2020/04/01/exploring-breath-and-space/">&lt;p&gt;This short grounding practice is designed to take less than 5 minutes and gives us a chance to pause and reconnect with
the present through our breath.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;padding:56.25% 0 0 0;position:relative;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/408244512?color=a6c7bd&amp;amp;byline=0&amp;amp;portrait=0&quot; style=&quot;position:absolute;top:0;left:0;width:100%;height:100%;&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; fullscreen&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/api/player.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to learn how to develop a deeper practice, &lt;a href=&quot;/contact&quot;&gt;chat to us&lt;/a&gt; about 1:1 &lt;a href=&quot;/modalities/somatic-explorations/&quot;&gt;Somatic Explorations&lt;/a&gt;
where you can explore and be supported as you gain a deeper understanding of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This short grounding practice is designed to take less than 5 minutes and gives us a chance to pause and reconnect with the present through our breath.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://somaticbalance.com.au/images/flower.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://somaticbalance.com.au/images/flower.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Name it to tame it</title><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/somatic%20explorations/2020/03/31/name-it-to-tame-it/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Name it to tame it" /><published>2020-03-31T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://somaticbalance.com.au/somatic%20explorations/2020/03/31/name-it-to-tame-it</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://somaticbalance.com.au/somatic%20explorations/2020/03/31/name-it-to-tame-it/">&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-quote&quot;&gt;  “In the brain, naming an emotion can help calm it. Here is where finding words to label an internal experience becomes
  really helpful. We can call this “Name it to tame it”... Your inner sea and your interpersonal relationships will all
  benefit from naming what is going on and bringing more integration into your life.”

  ― Daniel J. Siegel, Brainstorm: The Power and Purpose of the Teenage Brain
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s begin? I invite you to take a full, nurturing, rich breath, and as you let the air flow out effortlessly, bring
your attention to what you’re noticing in your body at this moment: it could be an emotion, a physical sensation, an
impulse towards doing… whatever it is, intend to find words to describe it - not explain or justify it, but describe it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Where is it in your body? ……………………………………………….&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What does it feel like? ……………………………………………….&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What words can you put around it? ……………………………………………….&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take as much time as you need to name what you’re noticing. And then take a few more deep breaths and repeat the process
one more time:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aim your awareness to what you’re noticing in your body, around your thoughts, or emotions, and whatever it is, intend
to find one or two words to describe it (don’t go into the story around it, just describe it). Again take time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Where is it in your body? ……………………………………………….&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What does it feel like? ……………………………………………….&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What words can you put around it? ……………………………………………….&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you’re feeling complete, take one more full breath in, and then notice how your experience of the present moment
has shifted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has anything changed for you? How is it helpful to pause for a moment and notice what’s happening for you? We hope you
can bring this practice into everyday moments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever you find yourself feeling too overwhelmed and when it’s difficult to process your inner world, come back to
this and &lt;strong&gt;name it to tame it&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like learn how to connect with what’s coming up for you, chat to us about 1:1 &lt;a href=&quot;/modalities/somatic-explorations/&quot;&gt;Somatic Explorations&lt;/a&gt;
where you can explore and be supported as you gain a deeper understanding of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">```quote “In the brain, naming an emotion can help calm it. Here is where finding words to label an internal experience becomes really helpful. We can call this “Name it to tame it”… Your inner sea and your interpersonal relationships will all benefit from naming what is going on and bringing more integration into your life.”</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://source.unsplash.com/ilox07iZ5iE/2000x1322?a=.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://source.unsplash.com/ilox07iZ5iE/2000x1322?a=.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Online Somatic Explorations &amp;amp; Meditations</title><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/community/somatic%20explorations/2020/03/24/online-somatic-meditation-course/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Online Somatic Explorations &amp; Meditations" /><published>2020-03-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://somaticbalance.com.au/community/somatic%20explorations/2020/03/24/online-somatic-meditation-course</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://somaticbalance.com.au/community/somatic%20explorations/2020/03/24/online-somatic-meditation-course/">&lt;p&gt;In these uncertain times, it’s equally important and challenging to be present and stay grounded. And that’s why I’m
offering these &lt;strong&gt;Somatic Meditations and Explorations&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal of this series is to support and deepen the process of coming back to the body, increasing somatic awareness
and connection to the present moment, through a succession of movement explorations and embodiment practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are welcome to practice with us no matter where you are at on your journey. The regular practice of these
embodiments and meditations can support you and bring many benefits, such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;increasing your body awareness, and contact with the present.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;releasing tension and improving posture.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;enhancing breathing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;achieving a greater sense of balance and stability.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;and since body and mind cannot be separate, you might notice more openness toward the environment and other people, a
sense of security and more energy overall.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following series have been inspired by my training in Rolfing, Embodied Counselling, Yoga -and some other
modalities- as well as on my own explorations of different types of somatic movement
practices, such as Hanna Somatics, Feldenkrais, and Rolfing movement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are meeting &lt;strong&gt;every Monday at 8:10 AM Sydney Time&lt;/strong&gt; to explore together for 15 minutes. These sessions are free of
charge and all you have to do is &lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot;&gt;contact me&lt;/a&gt; expressing your interest, and I’ll send you all the info so you
can join us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those wanting deeper explorations, I’m offering 1:1 sessions. Learn more about &lt;a href=&quot;/modalities/somatic-explorations/&quot;&gt;Somatic Explorations&lt;/a&gt;
and &lt;a href=&quot;/bookings/&quot;&gt;book a session&lt;/a&gt; today.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">In these uncertain times, it’s equally important and challenging to be present and stay grounded. And that’s why I’m offering these Somatic Meditations and Explorations.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://somaticbalance.com.au/images/meditation.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://somaticbalance.com.au/images/meditation.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Presenting: The Bookworms Cavern</title><link href="https://somaticbalance.com.au/community/2020/02/20/the-bookworms-cavern/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Presenting: The Bookworms Cavern" /><published>2020-02-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-02-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://somaticbalance.com.au/community/2020/02/20/the-bookworms-cavern</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://somaticbalance.com.au/community/2020/02/20/the-bookworms-cavern/">&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wished you could “read” someone? Maybe take a peek through their past stories and hopes for the future,
understand which pages of their life they have bookmarked as great memories? Well, now we might just be able to do that.
Introducing my latest project…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My inspiration comes from books - all those beautiful books out there waiting for us to reach out and make them our
companions and friends - and people - all those beautiful people out there waiting for …well, pretty much the same as
books, right? So how about creating a book club that’s about people instead of books? I can almost hear you say “What is
she talking about?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I present to you &lt;em&gt;“The Bookworm’s Cavern”&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We get together every 3 weeks. No tickets, or cost or anything like that.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You’re invited to bring one book with you that stood out in some way: it was the best you’ve ever read, the one that
inspired you to make some kind of change in your life, maybe it was the worst book you’ve ever read, or the most boring
one, maybe it’s the one you bought 3 years ago because you liked the cover and never got to read it, maybe it’s a
dictionary, maybe it’s the only one you have… doesn’t really matter, just one.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Through your experience with that book others are invited to have a peek into who you really are. By sharing what the
book meant to you, how you changed with it, how you felt, or why you hate the cover, you are sharing a piece of yourself
through it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We have a drink together; feel, talk, laugh or cry as needed, and then say goodbye with a hug (maybe?), and repeat
all of that again in 3 weeks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-am-i-expecting-will-happen&quot;&gt;What am I expecting will happen?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, for starters have some fun, meet people and be surrounded by books… that
alone sounds good enough to me. Maybe we’ll make friends, or read more and discover new books. Well, we’ll see about that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-im-not-expecting-will-happen&quot;&gt;What I’m not expecting will happen?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We all have to read the same book, or talk about it, or reflect on something, or
follow a tight structure, or workshop our life…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;when-are-we-meeting&quot;&gt;When are we meeting?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every three weeks on Thursday from 6:30 to 8:30 pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested? If so please &lt;a href=&quot;/contact/&quot;&gt;get it touch&lt;/a&gt; so I can add you to “The Bookworm’s Cavern” mailing list and keep you
posted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there and maybe borrow a book from you some time ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;COVID-19 is not stopping us! We’re just meeting in a virtual space for now.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Have you ever wished you could “read” someone? Maybe take a peek through their past stories and hopes for the future, understand which pages of their life they have bookmarked as great memories? Well, now we might just be able to do that. Introducing my latest project…</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://source.unsplash.com/6pO3QFkk7hQ/2000x1322?a=.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://source.unsplash.com/6pO3QFkk7hQ/2000x1322?a=.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>